A skeleton dating 200 years back
found in the Himalayas,
matched with the DNA
of his missing step-sister.
Shiharu?
It's true.
I believe you.
Haruka, there's something
you still don't know.
I wish to ask about my uncle's death.
Mari is gone.
Ishimizaki's daughter?
Why don't we work together,
for the sake of our own goals?
The remains Haruka was analyzing...
Were they given to Ishimizaki by Amol?
Yes, sir.
But now, this Amol has gone missing.
He was to attend a rather important meeting,
but continues to remain out of contact.
Police are currently searching
for his whereabouts.
Is this possibly related
to Professor Ishimizaki's case?
We have to erase all evidence of "log.0".
I will reassess our documents
on our associates.
If you'll excuse me.
The disappearance of those bones
and my uncle's death is no coincidence.
I agree.
Maybe a relative or loved one
wanted the remains back?
Maybe.
Was there anything odd about these bones?
You know something.
Please, tell me everything.
You left my uncle a voicemail.
It sounded urgent.
What were you going to ask about?
Stuff.
Do you know what a postdoc is?
They're essentially temp researchers.
Almost like a dispatch worker?
You could put it like that.
Postdocs either continue their research,
or give up and find jobs elsewhere.
Not the sort of conversation
I'd like to have in his lab.
You're lying.
My uncle often spoke of you.
He said you never consulted in anyone.
He hoped you one day would.
I'm just worried about Mari.
The culprit murdered my uncle.
They stole human remains without remorse.
What could they be doing to that poor girl?
We may find something
in the Professor's office.
This is where the bones were stolen.
But the lab is almost never empty.
There's a camera right outside as well.
And yet, the security tapes were wiped.
The culprit could enter here
without suspicion,
and knew where the cameras were...
Hey, I was in the middle of an interrogation.
I know. I don't doubt you.
The matching DNA sample
was also stolen, right?
Yeah.
What?
Professor Ishimizaki often holed up here
when he needed time alone.
Is this Mari?
I see she used to be so full of energy.
She was.
Did you know of her circumstances?
Yeah. I met her once.
When?
One of the times I'd gone to Yamashiro Park.
I only stopped to say hello.
Is this your daughter?
Yes. Her name is Mari.
Hello there.
[ishimizaki]
Do you know his password?
There's the one all our researchers use.
Guess that's not it.
Mind if I try?
[mari0808]
Mari's birthday.
Makes sense.
[Inbox - Search: Roopkund]
[No matching results]
Let's check his browsing history.
[Kayoko Senba]
Who is that?
Kayoko Senba?
She's a world-renowned
developmental biologist.
Now that I think about it,
I saw her at Professor Ishimizaki's funeral.
[Kayoko Senba, Guest Lecture]
Maybe he was going to attend her lecture?
[10:00AM-11:00AM - S]
That's the day he was murdered.
"S"...
"Senba"?
Did he have plans to see her that day?
What?
I heard people inside, but...
What are you doing here?
I accidentally deleted the thesis
I sent Professor Ishimizaki.
I hoped he had the email backed up.
I see.
I am Ishimizaki's niece.
It's nice to meet you.
Looks like he doesn't have it.
Guess I'll check my files again.
Sure.
- Shall we?
- Right.
I'll be locking up.
Okay.
Sorry, I let my guard down.
So, my uncle knew this Kayoko Senba.
Yeah.
Should we ask her about it?
Ask who?
You know.
[A mystery spanning two centuries]
[Matching the DNA of his step-sister]
Sir, your guest.
[log.2]
A diner would have sufficed.
Our conversation requires privacy, no?
I suppose.
- Want a drink?
- Water is enough, thank you.
Are you eating well?
For the most part.
Except when I'm busy.
I used to be just like you.
And Professor Ishimizaki as well?
I remember in our early days as researchers,
we'd go to horrendously cheap bars,
and talk bad about all our professors.
His passing deeply saddens me.
And while I'd rather not badmouth the dead,
those remains he had you analyze...
I suspect he acquired them through...
less scrupulous means.
What?
I hear over 800 human remains
were discovered around Roopkund.
All of which are precious for research.
So why analyze the DNA
of one particular skeleton?
I assume it was the work assigned to him.
This group of remains
spans generations, and nationalities.
Why analyze just one?
I suppose it is a bit odd.
What are you getting at?
There are collectors out there
who gather excavated human remains.
But those skeletons must first be analyzed
before they're sold.
Professor Ishimizaki
would never entertain the idea.
I agree with you.
However...
The researcher who sent him the bones
has gone missing in India.
Ishimizaki may have been involved
in some trouble.
He may have roped you into it as well.
You mentioned the DNA of the remains
was a perfect match to Shiharu's.
Yes. I redid the analysis multiple times.
I don't doubt you. I know you're thorough.
But maybe the error
was in the DNA sample itself.
Impossible. I know that was
Shiharu's hair I used.
You had Ishimizaki register it
during orientation, no?
You were still inexperienced at the time.
It's entirely possible he tricked you.
[Shiharu Nanase]
Why? What would his motive be?
I can't imagine his reasoning.
But it's my only working theory.
Shiharu's DNA couldn't match
that of a skeleton from two centuries ago.
Ultimately...
I'm not sure I trust Ishimizaki anymore.
Will you promise to keep this discussion
between us?
What we've said here
could tarnish his reputation.
It could put you in danger as well.
Promise me you won't do anything rash.
I can't stand to see you hurt any more.
Go see Dr. Furukawa.
She is an excellent psychiatrist.
I know she will be of use to you.
Alright.
I promise to go see her.
Really?
Professor Ishimizaki also said
I shouldn't worry you any further.
I see.
Isn't this the restaurant where we first met?
It took you this long to realize?
That's right.
This is indeed where we first met.
Wow, I've never been somewhere so fancy.
- Do you dine here often?
- No, not often.
Haruka, this man will become your father.
My name is Kyoichi Nanase.
It's nice to finally meet you.
Kyoichi also has a daughter named Shiharu.
I'm sure you two will learn to get along.
I'm sorry she couldn't join us today.
She was feeling sick.
No need to act so formal.
Want something to drink?
You're early.
The moving truck will be here in a moment.
Shiharu! Your mother and brother
have arrived.
Come on in.
Haruka, don't be a stranger. Come in.
I want you to remember me
with those eyes of yours.
Always.
Mother, I'll put your smoothie here.
Thank you.
Ubongo!
Wow, you got one already!
- A blue?
- Yes, one blue.
What color will be next?
You peeked!
Nuh-uh!
- See?
- Okay, okay.
Something the matter?
No, nothing.
That girl is one smart cookie, I tell you.
Grandma, again!
Yes, of course.
You won't win a second time.
I'll be heading out.
Mom's heading out later?
- Yeah. She's lecturing at Meiei Uni today.
- I see.
Good luck, Mom.
- Thanks.
- Bye, Daddy!
- Seven!
- Alright, seven. How do I play it?
I hear Haruka Nanase was a real mess
after his sister went missing?
Seems like it.
He self isolated, never spoke to anyone,
and always muttered to himself at night.
Yikes.
Agreed.
Sounds like a precarious individual,
doesn't he?
I thought you promised your father
you'd stay out of the case?
I only said that so he wouldn't worry.
- But I will go to the clinic.
- Are you ill?
My father assumes I'm acting delusional.
I see...
I'm not, alright?
So, what if Kayoko Senba ignores us?
You should smile.
Huh?
I said, you should smile.
I have nothing to smile about.
How can you, when Mari is missing?
"We don't laugh because we're happy -
we're happy, because we laugh."
What?
It's a quote from the philosopher,
William James.
I want to smile,
no matter how depressed I am.
I don't want to waste my life
wallowing in despair.
That makes no sense.
You should give it a try.
Come on, smile!
Satisfied?
It'll do.
[Kayoko Senba]
Humanity has slowly unraveled
the mysteries of life
by artificially manipulating,
and mimicking life's many phenomena.
Yet new discoveries in biology
are always met with criticism
from ethical,
and religious standpoints alike.
Both parties say we are
"bastardizing the miracle of life".
Yet know that we, biologists,
work with an utter respect for life.
This young boy is Keita.
He is my beloved grandchild.
Keita was born with a rare condition
called, "Phenylketonuria".
Those with phenylketonuria
are unable to process the amino acid,
phenylalanine.
As a result, they suffer from...
What is it?
- Stay here.
- Huh?
To those here who are involved in biology.
I hope you take great pride in your work,
and continue your research, without fail.
Thank you very much for listening.
Where did you go?
I'll explain later. Where's Kayoko Senba?
She's probably on her way out.
There's an exit out back.
Thank you, Dr. Senba.
Right this way.
- Excuse us.
- Did you need something?
We would like to speak with Dr. Senba.
I will take your questions.
- If you'll give us your contact...
- We'd like to speak to her directly.
Dr. Senba isn't accepting any assistants.
- No, that's not...
- Jeez, Haruka. Don't be shy.
I had just hoped to get her autograph.
Please don't take too much of her time.
Of course.
Smile.
Dr. Senba.
Yes?
I'm a huge fan.
May I have your autograph?
Oh my.
To think I had such young fans.
- Shall I hold that?
- Thank you.
Will a simple message do?
Of course.
What is your name?
Nanase.
"Nanase".
What does your father do?
He operates Nichie Pharmaceutical.
Ah, Kyoichi Nanase.
You knew of Professor Ishimizaki, yes?
I did. What about him?
I currently work for his laboratory.
How do you know my father,
and Professor Ishimizaki?
We used to do work together.
What sort of work?
I cannot say I remember.
It's been so long.
Doctor, you attended the Professor's funeral.
Dr. Senba must be going.
Please, don't you know anything
about Roopkund?
What are you talking about?
It's fine, he's no bother.
- But...
- You may leave us.
If you insist.
Thank you again, Doctor.
Those remains...
Not another word.
Do not look into it any further.
I say this for your own sake.
Now be on your way.
What did she mean by that?
I don't know.
But at the very least,
we've acquired Kayoko Senba's DNA.
Come in.
Sir.
All documents which cover "log.0"
have been disposed of.
Do you recall the man we encountered,
named Yoichi Onodera?
He's a freelance writer, who makes a killing
by blackmailing celebrities.
I remember him.
He seems to be looking into "log.0".
If he finds a lead,
he may sell the intel to Xin Ming Ah.
I understand.
Give me some time to think.
You must be Mr. Kojima,
the Japanese rep for Xin Ming Ah.
I hear Xin Ming Ah wants to buy out
Nichie Pharmaceutical.
But why Nichie Pharmaceutical?
Because you thought they'd be a cheap buy?
Their founder, Yumihiko Nanase,
is surrounded by nasty rumors.
Did you catch onto that?
- Did you?
- But of course.
Perhaps we even made the same realization.
And that is?
I'm referring to the Plantae.
If you want my intel, call me here.
Secure their sore point,
and the buy out will be a cinch.
I'm picking one hell of a fight here!
A guy with no sponsor,
raring up against a mega corp.
That guy will call back any minute now.
I sure got a big fish this time!
- The hell?
- This is my chance at redemption.
About damn time.
Give me another one.
Finally, they'll respect me.
And this man was watching her lecture?
Yeah.
The very guy I bumped into
on my way to the Professor's house.
He might be the culprit.
If he is, Kayoko Senba may be in danger.
What ties my uncle and Kayoko Senba together?
Maybe it is those bones.
I got this piece of hair
from the Professor's place.
Huh?
P-Professor...
Professor.
Professor Ishimizaki!
T-The police.
I only noticed the strand later.
If the DNA of this hair
and the saliva on this bottle match,
then it means Kayoko Senba
visited Professor Ishimizaki.
Right.
You didn't tell the police?
The police suspect me.
They wouldn't believe that
I "happened" to pick up this strand of hair.
Hirama, your phone.
Huh? Fix that.
Who the hell's calling now?
Onodera. How's the article coming?
I'm being hunted down right now.
Huh? What the...
Can you raise your voice?
Definitely not.
I've been running.
From who?
Some man I don't know. He's tailing me.
Tailing you?
What have you gotten yourself into?
Were you investigating gang work?
I was looking into Nichie.
Nichie Pharmaceutical?
What, are they creating
a new drug or something?
The founder was involved in some deep shit.
They wouldn't hunt you down
for something like that.
They're just ordinary corporate folk, right?
Then maybe it's Xin Ming Ah.
I met up with one of their men earlier.
Xin Ming Ah?
A conglomerate from China.
They're aiming to buy out
Nichie Pharmaceutical.
If they get me, I want you to disclose
all the documents I have at home.
Write an article, post it online...
just do something.
The keys to my apartment are in my mailbox.
Fine, just tell me where you are right now.
Right.
What? You alright?
I wanted to become a real journalist.
But that didn't bring food to the table.
So I became like every other hoodlum.
And now I'm paying the price.
Just tell me where you are.
I don't know.
I think I'm by the rooftops in Kanzai...
Onodera?
Damn it, where the hell is he?
- Go ask for details.
- Yes, sir.
Tada.
Hey, didn't realize you still did fieldwork.
I'm looking for a reporter named Onodera.
What happened here?
Not another murder, is it?
We're not sure yet.
There's a corpse, but we don't know whose.
It wouldn't happen to be this man, is it?
I couldn't tell.
Please, take a careful look.
No amount of looking will help.
It's just bones.
What?
The body's all bones. No decomposing, either.
It was a match.
[Complete DNA match]
Then Kayoko Senba went to my uncle's house.
She did.
Ubongo!
I lost again.
Again, Grandma.
Grandma?
Again!
Ask her directly?
Kayoko Senba would never entertain us.
Then let's ambush her outside her place.
It's time for your appointment at the clinic.
Your father instructed me
to drive you there.
Please, go on.
I'll meet you at her place.
You finally came to see me again.
I was worried about you, you know?
Sorry.
Here.
How do you feel?
Fine, thank you.
Your father was terribly worried about you.
I'm sorry for causing all the trouble.
Take it easy, I only want to talk today.
Yes, Doctor.
May I ask about your younger sister?
Go ahead.
Your sister suddenly came into your life,
upon your mother's remarriage, yes?
Right.
How did it feel, getting new family?
Were you happy? Annoyed?
At first, I was too embarrassed
to speak to her.
For an anti-social guy like myself,
it was quite the hurdle.
Learning to talk to her took time.
What's a particularly impactful memory
you have of her?
I had once told her of a theatre I visited
on my way back from school,
that only played the classics.
Because my mother was a busy woman,
and I had lost my father,
I would often kill time there.
That theatre felt like my one oasis.
And when I told her this,
she seemed to have an idea.
Where are we going?
To find my treasure.
What treasure?
Just follow me.
She never attended school,
and spent most of her time at home.
So in a way, she was quite sheltered.
We're here.
- Here?
- Yup.
Aren't we trespassing right now?
My father's company owns the building.
Therefore, it's mine.
That's some absurd reasoning.
"We are vehicles
programmed to preserve
the selfish molecules known as genes."
Richard Dawkins.
In here.
Come on.
Did you pity her?
Yes.
I wanted her to have her fun.
- Scared?
- No.
This room, here.
You sure we're allowed in here?
Of course.
Found it.
This is my treasure.
We're going downhill.
Watch out! Careful!
- Over there?
- Yup.
Alright.
- Almost there.
- I'm getting tired.
- Straight?
- That's right.
Alright, keep pushing.
You scared me!
No, that's for the speaker.
Wrong wire.
Ready, and...
- Done.
- Yeah.
Haruka, sit.
- I'll do it.
- No, let me.
I want to.
- Know how to use it?
- Yeah.
- Ready?
- Sure.
[Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Presents]
[Random Harvest]
Our story takes you down this shadowed path,
to a remote and guarded building
in the English Midlands:
Melbridge County Asylum.
Grimly proud to be...
Am I allowed to stay?
Huh?
You used to watch alone, didn't you?
to house the shattered minds...
- I want you to stay.
- of the war that was to end war.
That's a relief.
Now, Mr. and Mrs. Lloyd.
I should warn you.
- How can I ever repay you?
- That even if he is your son...
- He may not recognize you.
- For what?
- His memory is affected...
- This.
The result of shock.
He was picked up by the Germans,
in a shell hole near Arras, in 1917.
Just watch the movie.
Close to death,
and with no means of identification.
When he returned to consciousness
in a German hospital,
he could remember nothing at all
of his past life.
He had no name... He had no family
with whom he could correspond.
Six months ago, he was exchanged
through Switzerland and sent here.
Such beautiful eyes.
Huh?
I want you to remember me
with those eyes of yours.
Always.
Sure.
Don't move.
You must be admitted to a ward.
What?
Your father told me everything.
He said you experience intense delusions,
and are a real danger to those around you.
You must be admitted at once.
This was your plan all along.
Stay calm, it's just a stabilizer.
Wait!
He escaped?
Please don't cause any more of a fuss.
Excuse me.
Show me.
Yes, ma'am.
So this is...
Yes.
A skeleton from Roopkund.